KSHITIJ PANDE

PERSONAL PROFILE

II am a web Developer who specializes in creating dynamic and beautiful web pages. I have been in the field for nearly a year, and have been loving every minute of it. I graduated in 2016 with a bachelor's degree in Bachelor's of Computer Applications(BCA) and pursuing Masters in Computer Applications(MCA). I am a designer, developer, and overall thinker...

EXTRA CURRICULAR

- Head Cultural Co-Ordinator
- Member of Placement team

CONTACT INFORMATION

Mobile Number:7709971395

kshitijpandekp@gmail.com

kshitijpande.github.io

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Communication Skills
- Management Skills
- Leadership Skills
- Time Management
- Punctuality

HOBBIES

- Photography
- Cricket
- Guitar
- Sketching

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

INTERN WEB DEVELOPER

Webmatrix Technologies, Pune, Maharashtra / July 2017 - May 2018

11 months of experience in Web-Developement including Wordpress and Joomla.

ASSOCIATE

Wipro BPS / December 2016 - March 2017

Worked as Associate in Wipro BPS for 3 Months.

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE

Jaihind High School, Dhule, Maharashtra / June 2010 -May 2011

HIGHER SECONDARY CERTIFICATE

Yashwantrao Mohite College, Pune, Maharashtra / June 2012 - May 2013

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS(BCA)

Sinhgad College Of Science, Pune, Maharashtra / June 2013 - May 2016

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS(MCA)

Institute of Management and Career Courses(IMCC) / Pursuing

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS/Bootstrap
- WordPress
- Joomla
- PHP